rsvpify.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy - RSVPify

### OVERVIEW

This Privacy Policy details the collection, use, transfer and retention of data and the related principles, policies and procedures of RSVPify LLC (“RSVPify,” we, us) and any application, feature, functionality, or digital asset owned by RSVPify (our “Services”).

RSVPify is committed to the safety and security of its platform and Services, and the privacy of its users and their data. RSVPify abides by several core privacy principles including (1) notice, (2) choice, (3) accountability for onward transfer, (4) security, (5) data integrity and purpose limitation, (6) access and (7) recourse, enforcement and liability.

### COMPLIANCE & CERTIFICATION WITH THE EU-U.S. PRIVACY SHIELD FRAMEWORK

RSVPify complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. RSVPify has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.   
If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view RSVPify’s certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.

RSVPify’s compliance with the Privacy Shield is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In further adherence to Privacy Shield Principles and to the extent allowed by law, RSVPify may be held potentially and partially liable in the event that a third party processes Personal Data on our behalf and at our express direction in a manner failing to adhere to these Privacy Shield Principles and where alleged damage is incurred as a direct result of this failure.

### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can browse RSVPify.com and use select Services without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. If, on the other hand, you register for an account with us, you give us your personal information, and you are not anonymous. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States.

We collect limited personal information in order to provide you with the use of and access to our site, applications, services and tools, and to help us personalize and improve your experience.

Information we collect automatically: When you visit our site, use our applications, services, and tools, and/or interact with our advertising or content, we automatically collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile device, or other access device. This information is associated with you personally only when sign in as a registered user, and includes but is not limited to:

  * device ID or unique identifier, device type, geo-location information, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the site, referral URL, ad data, IP address, and standard web log information,
  * anonymous information collected through our use cookies and web beacons.

Information you give us: We collect and store any information you enter on RSVPify.com or you provide to us in context of using RSVPify’s Services. This may include, but is not limited to:

  * information you provide us when registering for an account, including email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, physical contact information, and financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;
  * additional information you may provide to us via social media site or services;
  * transactional information based on your activities on the site
  * information provided in the context of community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our site, or correspondence sent to us;
  * additional personal information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID or bill to verify your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity).

### TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA

The Services are hosted and operated in the United States (“U.S.“), with development, support, and maintenance operations in other countries. If you do not reside in the U.S., laws in the U.S. (and other countries) may differ from the laws where you reside. By using the Service, you acknowledge that any Personal Data about you, regardless of whether provided by you or obtained from a third party, is being provided to RSVPify in the U.S. and will be hosted on U.S. servers, and you authorize RSVPify to transfer, store, host and process your information to and in the U.S., and possibly other countries. By providing information to RSVPify, you consent to the storage of your Personal Information in the United States, irregardless of where you reside.

If you reside in the EU or Switzerland, you hereby consent to the transfer of your data to the U.S. pursuant to EU-U.S. or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks.

### RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA

  1. ACCESS: You may access and manage select Personal Data that RSVPify holds about you by logging into your account or contacting us.
  2. DELETION: You may request that we delete all or select personal data related to you or your account.
  3. CORRECTION: If you believe that RSVPify holds incorrect Personal Data that requires correction, you may request that we update your your data.
  4. LIMITATION: RSVPify limits the use and transfer of your Personal Data for the express purposes of the provision, support and limited marketing of our Services.
  5. OPT-OUT: You have the right to opt-out of certain uses and disclosures of your Personal Information. Where you have consented to RSVPify Processing of your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information, you may withdraw that consent at any time and opt-out to further Processing by contacting us at support@rsvpify.zendesk.com. Even if you opt-out, we may still collect and use non-Personal Information regarding your activities on our Sites and/or information from the advertisements on Third-Party websites for non-interest based advertising purposes, such as to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements.

You may further request additional information about the Personal Data that we hold about you, request deletion or correction of Personal Data, and receive further detail on the limitations of our use of your Personal Data by emailing privacy@rsvpify.com.

_Email And Telephone Communications_ : If you receive an unwanted email from us, you can use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email to opt-out of receiving future emails. We will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. Note that you must click on the unsubscribe list to be removed from our marketing lists as reaching out to individual members of our support team will not qualify you for removal. Note that you will continue to receive transaction-related emails regarding products or Services you have requested. We may also send you certain non-promotional communications regarding RSVPify and our Services and you will not be able to opt-out of those communications (e.g., communications regarding updates to our Terms or this Privacy Policy).

_Mobile Devices_ : RSVPify may occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications with information that may be of interest to you. You may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of communications by changing the settings on your mobile device. RSVPify may also collect location-based information if you use our mobile applications. You may opt-out of this collection by changing the settings on your mobile device.

_“Do Not Track”_ : Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. Please note that we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

_Cookies And Interest-Based Advertising_ : As noted above, you may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt-out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.

The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from our data partners and our other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these, and also learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy, at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, or http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ and www.aboutads.info/choices/.

To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted-out on your computer browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt-out on each device. Advertisements on Third-Party websites that contain the AdChoices link and that link to this Privacy Policy may have been directed to you based on anonymous, non-Personal Information collected by advertising partners over time and across websites. These advertisements provide a mechanism to opt-out of the advertising partners’ use of this information for interest-based advertising purposes.

### RIGHT TO OBJECT AND LODGE A COMPLAINT

We take all concerns and complaints related to your privacy and Personal Data seriously.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, RSVPify commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information in a timely manner. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact RSVPify by one of these means:

Email Us:

privacy@rsvpify.com

Write To Us:

RSVPify LLC  
20 W Kinzie  
Floor 17  
Chicago, IL 60618

RSVPify has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States.

If you do not receive acknowledgment and resolution of your concern or complaint from us within 45 days, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit https://www.jamsadr.com/ for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you. In certain circumstances and barring the resolution of your complaint by other means, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration of your complaint.

### MOBILE

When you download or use our Mobile Applications, or access one of our mobile optimized sites, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to control or disable location services in the device’s setting’s menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device’s location services, we recommend you contact your mobile service carrier or the manufacture of your particular device.

### INFORMATION FROM OTHER SOURCES

We may receive or collect supplemental information about you from third parties sources and add it to our account information. This may include, but is not limited to, demographic, navigation information, additional contact information, credit check information, and additional information about you from credit bureaus or other sources, as permitted by law.

### INFORMATION SHARING & REGISTRATION WITH SOCIAL MEDIA SITE

We offer sign-on services that allow you to use third party login credentials to access the RSVPify site or related site. We also offer services that allow you to share information with third party social media website such as Facebook, Google Plus, Twitter, and others.

You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by such third party website. The personal information we have access to varies by website and is controlled your by privacy settings on that website and your consent. By associating an account managed by a third party with your RSVPify account and authorizing RSVPify to have access to this information, you agree that RSVPify may collect, use and store information from these website in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with access to our site and/or use of our services, applications and tools, provide you with requested customer service and relevant information about your account and our services, and to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * provide you access to our site and the Services and customer support you request;
  * prevent, detect, and investigate, fraud, security breaches, potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * contact you, either via email or telephone, to resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems with your account or our site, services, applications or tools, or for other purposes authorized by law;
  * contact you, either via email or telephone to inform you about our services and those of our corporate family, deliver targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;  
compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties;
  * contact you at any telephone number using auto-dialed or pre-recorded message calls or text (SMS) messages (if applicable) as authorized for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy;
  * provide you other services requested by you as described when we collect the information.

### MARKETING

Personally identifiable information including but not limited to your contact information (name, email address, phone number, billing address, etc.) and that of your guests is kept strictly confidential, and will never be sold, or rented. RSVPify will not market its services or the services of its partners to your guests, but may from time to time send marketing-related emails to registered users of RSVPify.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, clickstream information, browser type, device IDs, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites. in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These advertising partners may use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering targeted advertisements to you when you visit non-RSVPify related websites within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “online behavioral advertising". We may allow access to other data collected by the Site to facilitate transmittal of information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your Personal Information with Third-Party advertising partners, you may opt-out of such sharing at no cost by following the instructions in below (after the Disclosure of your Personal Information section).

### OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that content or information violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws and regulations. As stated above, we do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.  
We may also share your personal information with:

  * Members of the RSVPify corporate family to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions, and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts, violations of our policies, fraud and/or data security breaches, and to guide decisions about their products, site, applications, services and tools, and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you have requested their services and will use your personal information in compliance with their this Privacy Policy and our global privacy standards.
  * Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as, but not limited to, fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs, site operations, and co-branded credit cards).
  * Financial institution partners of RSVPify corporate family members who offer financial products (such as PayPal) to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts, violations of our policies, fraud and/or security breaches, and to guide decisions about their products, website, applications, services and tools, and communications. These third party financial institution partners will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you have requested their services and will use your personal information in compliance their respective privacy policies and consistent with this privacy policy and our global privacy standards
  * Other RSVPify users, whether located in your country of residence or outside of your country of residence, as authorized by you or your use of our site, services, applications or tools. For example, where you are involved in a transaction with another user, the other user may view your email address and request and obtain your contact information and postal address to help complete the transaction;
  * Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).
  * Law enforcement, governmental agencies, or authorized third-parties, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation, national security concern, or alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other RSVPify user to legal liability. In such events, we will only disclose information relevant and necessary to the investigation or inquiry, such as name, city, state, ZIP code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and anything else we may deem relevant to the investigation.
  * Credit bureaus with which we may report information about your account, including information on late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account may be reflected in your credit report.
  * Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.).

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

### USING INFORMATION FROM RSVPIFY

We encourage you to disclose your privacy practices and respect the privacy of other users. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information. To help protect your privacy, we offer a number of tools and measures to mitigate the possibility of unauthorized account access or access to our RSVP system.

### HOW WE USE COOKIES

When you access our website, or use our applications and/or services and tools, we may place small data files on your computer or other device. We use these data files, commonly known as “Cookies", to help us identify you as a user, customize our services, content and advertising, to measure promotional effectiveness, and to promote trust and safety.

A few important things you should know about our use of Cookies:

  * We offer certain features that are available only through the use of Cookies
  * We use both session and persistent Cookies. Session Cookies expire and no longer have any effect when you log out of your account or close your browser. Persistent Cookies remain on your device until you erase them or they expire
  * You are always free to decline Cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of our website, applications, and/or services and tools. Refer to the Opt-Out section above and the help section of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling Cookies
  * We encode and protect our Cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them
  * You may encounter Cookies from third parties, known as service providers, that we have allowed on our site that assist us with various aspects of our web site operations and services
  * You also may encounter Cookies from third parties on certain pages of the website that we do not control and have not authorized. (For example, if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a cookie placed by that web page)

### NO SPAM, SPYWARE OR SPOOFING

We and our users do not tolerate spam. Make sure to set your RSVPify communication preferences so we communicate to you as you prefer. You are not licensed to add other RSVPify users, even a user who has purchased an item from you, to your mailing list (email or physical mail) without their express consent.

REPORTING SPAM: To report RSVPify-related spam or spoof emails to RSVPify, please forward the email to support@RSVPify.zendesk.com.

You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our Terms of Service. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content, but we do not permanently store messages sent through these tools

### ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your RSVPify password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify RSVPify and change your password.

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing on to RSVPify. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate.

### THIRD PARTIES

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others on our site or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you provide to them. RSVPify does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### DATA RETENTION

RSVPify retains the Personal Information we receive as described in this Privacy Policy for as long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, pursue legitimate business purposes, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws.

### CONTACT US

Email Us:

privacy@rsvpify.com

Write To Us:

RSVPify LLC  
20 W Kinzie  
Floor 17  
Chicago, IL 60618

—

LAST UPDATED

January 24, 2019
